$RIMSTART_T0	Initial Setup
$RIMSTART_D0	Please wait while setup is in progress.
$RIMSTART_T1	Birthsign
$RIMSTART_D1	Choose your birthsign. This is different from Standing Stones you can find in game and you cannot change your birthsign later.
$RIMSTART_T2	Skills
$RIMSTART_D2	Select your Major & Minor skills.
$RIMSTART_T3	Deity
$RIMSTART_D3	You can change this later, although your favor with your previous divine does not carry over.
$RIMSTART_T4	Traits
$RIMSTART_D4	Character traits. An optional third trait is unlocked after you finish one of guild questlines or beat one of the three bosses of the game.
$RIMSTART_T5	Game Mode
$RIMSTART_D5	You can swap this out at any time under Settings > Difficulty menu.
